<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team Maya on Portfolio Project</title>
    <link>/en/author/team-maya/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team Maya on Portfolio Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 16:23:19 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/author/team-maya/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making the Blog Accessible on the Web</title>
      <link>/en/gallery/blog-acessivel-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 16:23:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/gallery/blog-acessivel-web/</guid>
      <description>Initially we registered for access to the AWS website, We started a virtual machine using EC2,
AWS, running the Amazon Linux 2 distribution.
 We perform the updates of the VM&amp;rsquo;s operating system (with the command: sudo yum update)
and we installed the Apache service to create the blog Host on the web,
for that it was necessary to compile the blog.
In order to make the blog structure easier to access, we installed git so that we can clone, transfer files and version the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Changes</title>
      <link>/en/article/alteracaotema/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 20:25:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/alteracaotema/</guid>
      <description>We modified the Bilburry theme to better accommodate our project, the theme itself doesn’t have the buttons on the main tab, we implemented them using HTML and SASS to make the types of post we create more organized, we also changed the options from standard languages ​​that are English and German to Portuguese (standard) and English. When the English option is clicked, the site loads an English version of the posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools Used</title>
      <link>/en/article/tech-stack/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 22:25:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/tech-stack/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Static Gen: Hugo To start building the blog, we selected a Static Gen (Static Site Generator) called Hugo, its function is to serve as the basis for a customizable theme. Together with Hugo, we installed a theme called Billburry, the theme deals with the visual part of the blog, while Hugo with the code part. Hugo has a server internal, using it we can generate a &amp;ldquo;preview&amp;rdquo; with the changes we made to the theme, after making considerable changes, we send the changes to our repository on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>