<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quem somos on Portfolio Project</title>
    <link>localhost:1313/en/tags/quem-somos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quem somos on Portfolio Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:53:11 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="localhost:1313/en/tags/quem-somos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Gabriel Vilela Serra</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:53:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_gabriel/</guid>
      <description>Introduced in the world of computers and games since I was 6 years old, computing has been a great passion for me since I was little. The curiosity to know how the games worked led me to the programming path. In 2013, the Java language was introduced to make a modification of the best game of the time, Minecraft. In the years that followed, I explored more languages ​​like C # to use on Unity, which is a game engine that was starting to become popular at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is João Pedro Larini</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_joao/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:53:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_joao/</guid>
      <description>Interested in computing from an early age, I always seek to update myself on new types of technology, both for professional use how much staff. I have complete courses in the area of servers, technical maintenance and hardware theory. Currently studying science computing. I participated in several lectures discussing innovations proposed by companies like Amazon, Sotran, Google and others. I intend to professionalize in the area of servers and database and provide services reported to the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Heber Junior?</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_heber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:52:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/en/article/quemsomos_heber/</guid>
      <description>Currently studying Computer Science, I usually research on the subject since I was a child, in order to facilitate everyday tasks. I am interested in the area of ​​information security, cryptography, social structure and malware, I believe that the area is currently little known and deserves greater attention, given the importance that information manipulation has over other areas. I intend to continue my studies on systems structures and be able to add as much information to the IT community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>