<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Atualizacoes on Portfolio Project</title>
    <link>/en/tags/atualizacoes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Atualizacoes on Portfolio Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:25:43 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/tags/atualizacoes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Registrando e Configurando o Domínio</title>
      <link>/en/article/adicionandodomain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:25:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/adicionandodomain/</guid>
      <description>The most challenging part of registering a domain is choosing the name &amp;hellip; So many creative possibilities, interesting combinations, and funny ones too. We contemplate acquiring names like ronaldinho.soccer, maya.team, teammata.wtf, among many others. In the end, we chose teammaya.codes, which matches the purpose of the site, and even sounds good. One of the main reasons that led to this choice was the fact that I got the Student package from GitHub, which gave me a 100% discount on the first domain from the provider Name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making the Blog Accessible on the Web</title>
      <link>/en/gallery/blog-acessivel-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 16:23:19 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/gallery/blog-acessivel-web/</guid>
      <description>Initially we registered for access to the AWS website, We started a virtual machine using EC2,
AWS, running the Amazon Linux 2 distribution.
 We perform the updates of the VM&amp;rsquo;s operating system (with the command: sudo yum update)
and we installed the Apache service to create the blog Host on the web,
for that it was necessary to compile the blog.
In order to make the blog structure easier to access, we installed git so that we can clone, transfer files and version the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Changes</title>
      <link>/en/article/alteracaotema/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 20:25:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/alteracaotema/</guid>
      <description>We modified the Bilburry theme to better accommodate our project, the theme itself doesn’t have the buttons on the main tab, we implemented them using HTML and SASS to make the types of post we create more organized, we also changed the options from standard languages ​​that are English and German to Portuguese (standard) and English. When the English option is clicked, the site loads an English version of the posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>