<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gabriel Vilela Serra on Portfolio Project</title>
    <link>/en/author/gabriel-vilela-serra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gabriel Vilela Serra on Portfolio Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:25:43 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/author/gabriel-vilela-serra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Registrando e Configurando o Domínio</title>
      <link>/en/article/adicionandodomain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:25:43 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/adicionandodomain/</guid>
      <description>The most challenging part of registering a domain is choosing the name &amp;hellip; So many creative possibilities, interesting combinations, and funny ones too. We contemplate acquiring names like ronaldinho.soccer, maya.team, teammata.wtf, among many others. In the end, we chose teammaya.codes, which matches the purpose of the site, and even sounds good. One of the main reasons that led to this choice was the fact that I got the Student package from GitHub, which gave me a 100% discount on the first domain from the provider Name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms Animator</title>
      <link>/en/video/animadoralgoritmos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 16:23:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/video/animadoralgoritmos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A very interesting project that I worked with João was the project of the algorithm animator, which we did in the discipline Computer Laboratory II of professor Ricardo Inacio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the video above, I demonstrate how this program works, and also mention the difficulties encountered along the way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldinho Soccer 64</title>
      <link>/en/video/hahaharonaldinhosoccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 16:23:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/video/hahaharonaldinhosoccer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best memes of 2020. Period.
Why does it exist? Why did something like that become a meme? Nobody knows. But something about this introduction to a bootleg game made for the Brazilian market and developed by a Peruvian company is too funny for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s sarcastic laugh (?), Along with a possibly Peruvian person speaking a Brazilian name and an English word in quick succession.
Perhaps the soundtrack, that the more you hear, the more you want to hear. Something tells me that we&amp;rsquo;ll never know for sure &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is Gabriel Vilela Serra</title>
      <link>/en/article/quemsomos_gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:53:11 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/article/quemsomos_gabriel/</guid>
      <description>Introduced in the world of computers and games since I was 6 years old, computing has been a great passion for me since I was little. The curiosity to know how the games worked led me to the programming path. In 2013, the Java language was introduced to make a modification of the best game of the time, Minecraft. In the years that followed, I explored more languages ​​like C # to use on Unity, which is a game engine that was starting to become popular at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>